seventhqueen.com 2019-04-09

# Privacy Policy - SeventhQueen

_Last Updated: September, 04 2018_

### INTRODUCTION

SeventhQueen, LLC (referred to as “we”, “us” or “our”) have established this privacy policy to provide you with details of how we collect and process your personal data through your use of our website, seventhqueen.com.

It is very important that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date. Please let us know if at any time your personal information changes by emailing us at hi@seventhqueen.com.

By providing us with your data, you warrant to us that you are over 13 years of age.

### WHAT DATA DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU, FOR WHAT PURPOSE AND ON WHAT GROUND WE PROCESS IT

You can visit our website without revealing any personal data. However, we need certain personal information if you wish to purchase certain products, receive our newsletter, or use certain services. Personal data means any information capable of identifying an individual. It does not include anonymized data.

We may process the following categories of personal data about you:

 _Communication Data_  that includes any communication that you send to us whether that be through the contact form on our website, through email, text, social media messaging, social media posting or any other communication that you send us. We process this data for the purposes of communicating with you, for considering job applications, for record keeping and for the establishment, pursuance or defence of legal claims. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to reply to communications sent to us, processing job applications, to keep records and to establish, pursue or defend legal claims.

 _Customer Data_  that includes data relating to any purchases of goods and/or services such as your name, title, billing address, home address, email address, phone number, contact details, profile photo, purchase details and your partly anonymized card details. We process this data to supply the products and/or services you have purchased, validating product licenses, and to keep records of such transactions. Our lawful ground for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps at your request to enter into such a contract.

 _User Data_  that includes data about how you use our website and any online services together with any data that you post for publication on our website or through other online services. We process this data to operate our website and ensure relevant content is provided to you, to ensure the security of our website, to maintain back-ups of our website and/or databases and to enable publication and administration of our website, other online services and business. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to enable us to properly administer our website and our business.

 _Technical Data_  that includes data about your use of our website and online services such as your IP address, your login data, details about your browser, length of visit to pages on our website, page views and navigation paths, details about the number of times you use our website, time zone settings and other technology on the devices you use to access our website. The source of this data is from our analytics tracking system. We process this data to analyse your use of our website and other online services, to administer and protect our business and website, to deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and to understand the effectiveness of our advertising. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to enable us to properly administer our website and our business and to grow our business and to decide our marketing strategy.

We may use  _Customer Data, User Data and Technical Data_  to deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you (including Facebook adverts or other display advertisements) and to measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve you. Our lawful ground for this processing is legitimate interests which is to grow our business. We may also use such data to send other marketing communications to you. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests (namely to grow our business).

 _Recruitment Data_  which may include your CV or resume, online profile, written application, responses to questions, interview notes and information passed to us from former employers, in addition to any Communication Data listed above. We use this to assess job applications. Our lawful ground for this processing is legitimate interests, which in this case are to find the very best candidates to work for us.

We do not collect any sensitive data about you. Sensitive data refers to data such as your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, political opinions, information about your health and genetic and biometric data. We do not collect any information about criminal convictions and offenses.

Where we are required to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of the contract between us and you do not provide us with that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract (for example, to provide products or services to you). If you don’t provide us with the requested data, we may have to cancel a product or service you have ordered but if we do, we will notify you at the time.

We will only use your personal data for a purpose it was collected for or a reasonably compatible purpose if necessary. For more information on this please email us at hi@seventhqueen.com. In case we need to use your details for an unrelated new purpose we will update this privacy policy.

We may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent where this is required or permitted by law.

### HOW WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We may collect data about you by you providing the data directly to us (for example by filling in forms on our site or by sending us emails). We may automatically collect certain data from you as you use our website by using cookies and similar technologies.

We may receive data from third parties such as analytics providers such as Google, advertising networks such as Facebook, such as search information providers such as Google, providers of technical, payment and delivery services, such as data brokers or aggregators.

We may also collect data from publicly available sources such as social media profiles and in the case of job applications, we may also obtain personal data from former employers.

### MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS

Our lawful ground of processing your personal data to send you marketing communications is our legitimate interests.

Under the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations, we may send you marketing communications from us if:

  * You made a purchase or asked for information from us about our goods or services; or
  * You agreed to receive marketing communications and in each case you have not opted out of receiving such communications since; or
  * You registered on our site to access support and other services. You can opt out of receiving emails from us at any time.

We do not share your personal data with any third party for their own marketing purposes. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

You can ask us to stop sending you messages at any time by following the opt-out links on any message sent to you or OR by emailing us at hi@seventhqueen.com at any time.

If you opt-out of receiving communication, this opt-out does not apply to personal data provided as a result of other transactions, such as purchases or for the fulfilment of services.

### DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We may share your personal data with the parties set out below:

  * Service providers who provide IT and system administration services.
  * Professional advisers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers.
  * Government bodies that require us to report processing activities.
  * Contractors who use your personal data in the course of activities for which they are contracted.
  * Third parties to whom we sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets.

We require all third parties to whom we transfer your data to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We only allow such third parties to process your personal data for specified purposes only.

### TRANSFER OF DATA

Where we transfer your data to third parties, we will only do so where those parties agree to keep this information confidential. As such:

  * We may transfer data to service providers who are part of the EU-US Privacy Shield; or
  * Where we use certain service providers or contractors, we may use specific contracts or codes of conduct or certification mechanisms that are compliant with both US privacy laws and the EU General Data Protection Regulation.

If neither of the above safeguards is available, we may request your explicit consent to the specific transfer. You will have the right to withdraw this consent at any time.

### DATA SECURITY

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your personal and non-personal data is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, we may use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

We have put in place security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used, altered, disclosed, or accessed without authorization. We also allow access to your personal data only to those employees and partners who have a business need to know such data.

We have procedures in place to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach if we are legally required to.

### DATA RETENTION

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

When deciding what the correct time is to keep the data for we look at its amount, nature and sensitivity, potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure, the processing purposes, if these can be achieved by other means and legal requirements.

In some circumstances we may anonymize your personal data for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

### Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. SeventhQueen aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  *  **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.**  Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
  *  **The right of rectification.**  You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  *  **The right to object.**  You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  *  **The right of restriction.**  You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  *  **The right to data portability.**  You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
  *  **The right to withdraw consent.**  You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where SeventhQueen relied on your consent to process your personal information.

You can see more about these rights at: [https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/).

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive or refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you.

Under the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) we are required to nominate a supervisory authority within the EU for our EU customers. Therefore, if you are an EU citizen and wish to make a complaint regarding our collection and use of your data, we would refer you to the Data Protection Commissioner in Ireland: [https://www.dataprotection.ie](https://www.dataprotection.ie/).

However, before making a complaint to any supervisory authority, regardless of your location, we would ask you to contact us first, so that we can try to resolve it for you.

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analysing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

#### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

  *  **Google Analytics  **is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
  *  **Intercom  **We use third-party analytics services to help understand your usage of our services. In particular, we provide a limited amount of your information (such as sign-up date and some personal information like your email address) to Intercom, Inc. (“Intercom”) and utilize Intercom to collect data for analytics purposes when you visit our website or use our product. As a data processor acting on our behalf, Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or product and tracks our relationship by way of cookies and similar technologies so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on Intercom’s use of cookies, please visit <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#cookie-policy>. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s). As part of our service agreements, Intercom collects publicly available contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender, company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses, to enhance your user experience. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit [https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy](https://protect-eu.mimecast.com/s/zMP6C0glXI29np7TOQGei?domain=intercom.com). Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use which can be found at [https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms](https://protect-eu.mimecast.com/s/_s9hCg5BQCljvDoc7KDEG?domain=intercom.com). If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please contact us.

#### Google Web Fonts

For uniform representation of fonts, this page uses web fonts provided by Google. When you open a page, your browser loads the required web fonts into your browser cache to display texts and fonts correctly.

For this purpose your browser has to establish a direct connection to Google servers. Google thus becomes aware that our web page was accessed via your IP address. The use of Google Web fonts is done in the interest of a uniform and attractive presentation of our plugin. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO.

If your browser does not support web fonts, a standard font is used by your computer

#### Behavioral Remarketing

SeventhQueen uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

  *  **Google AdWords**  remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
  *  **Facebook  **remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada <http://youradchoices.ca/> or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: <https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>

#### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

  *  **PayPal**  Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

### CONSENT

If you object to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal data as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal data to us. If you have provided personal information to us but now object to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please email us at hi@seventhqueen.com.

### THIRD-PARTY LINKS

This website may include links to third-party websites, plugins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit.

### MEDIA

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### COMMENTS

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### CONTACT FORMS

When you submit a contact form on our website, we collect the data shown in the contact form and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. We keep contact form submissions for an unlimited period for customer service purposes, but we do not use the information submitted  for marketing purposes.

### EMBEDDED CONTENT FROM OTHER SITES

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### COOKIES

A “cookie” is a piece of information that is stored on your computer’s hard drive and which records how you move your way around a website so that, when you revisit that website, it can present tailored options based on the information stored about your last visit. Cookies can also be used to analyze traffic and for advertising and marketing purposes. Cookies are used by nearly all websites and do not harm your system.

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly. For more information about the cookies we use, please see [this page](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie).

We use cookies to track your use of our website. This enables us to understand how you use the site and track any patterns with regards how you are using our website. This helps us to develop and improve our website as well as products and/or services in response to what you might need or want. Cookies are either:

 _Session Cookies_  – These are only stored on your computer during your web session and are automatically deleted when you close your browser. They usually store an anonymous session ID allowing you to browse a website without having to log in to each page but they do not collect any personal data from your computer; or

 _Persistent Cookies_  – A persistent cookie is stored as a file on your computer and it remains there when you close your web browser. The cookie can be read by the website that created it when you visit that website again. We use persistent cookies for Google Analytics.

Cookies can also be categorised as follows.

 _Strictly Necessary Cookies_  – These cookies are essential to enable you to use the website effectively, such as when buying a product and / or service, and therefore cannot be turned off. Without these cookies, the services available to you on our website cannot be provided. These cookies do not gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you have been on the internet.

 _Performance Cookies_  – These cookies enable us to monitor and improve the performance of our website. For example, they allow us to count visits, identify traffic sources and see which parts of the site are most popular.

 _Functionality Cookies_  – These cookies allow our website to remember choices you make and provide enhanced features. For instance, we may be able to provide you with news or updates relevant to the services you use. They may also be used to provide services you have requested such as viewing a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect is usually anonymized.

Please note that third parties who advertise on our website (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

From time to time, we may revise this privacy policy as we see fit. When we do, we will also revise the “last update” date, which can be found at the top of the policy. We encourage you to review this policy periodically as we may not provide you with notice of revisions . If you continue to use our website after we have revised this policy, this will signify your acceptance of it.

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please contact us by email, at hi@seventhqueen.com.
